鉴于你在无存知地的表现
You don't get to ask questions
你没有权利提问
after the nonsense you pulled on Knowhere.
我可救了奎尔
I just saved Quill.
我们已经讨论过了
We've already established
你们想炸了我乘坐的飞船  那可不是在救我
that you destroying the ship that I'm on is not saving me.
我们什么时候讨论过了
When did we establish it?
就几秒钟以前
Like three seconds ago!
我没在仔细听  那会儿正走神
I wasn't listening. I was thinking of something else.
她说得没错  你没有发表意见的权利
She's right. You don't get an opinion.
你有百分之多少的计划
What percentage?
我不知道  百分之十二吧
I don't know. Twelve percent.
百分之十二?
Twelve percent?
你笑得真假
That's a fake laugh.
是真的  -太假了
It's real! - Totally fake.
这是我这辈子笑得最真实
That is the most real, authentic,
最歇斯底里的一次了
hysterical laugh of my entire life
因为你这是狗屁计划
because that is not a plan.
只能算是一个想法
It's barely a concept.